A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Director of the Virginia Housing Development Authority, 1972-2012
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence, subject files and board meeting records (Accession 44409), 1983-1987., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  - Administative Services: Annual Report, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: Articles of interest, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Administative Services: Support Services, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Exective Director, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Executive Director - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Commissioners, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - U.S. Legislators, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Division Director Retreat, 1984 (Box 5)
  - Senator Buchanan, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Harrison School Dedication, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Affordable Housing in Reagan Administration, 1985 (Box 5)
  - VCU Urban Housing Policy class, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Home Manufacturers Association, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Bond Hearing, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Renaissance Cookie Contest, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Commerce and Resources Retreat, 1985 (Box 5)
  - NHC Annual Meeting, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Rural Homesteading Kickoff, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Treasury Dept. MRB hearing, 1985 (Box 5)
  - American Planning Association, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Strategic Planning in Local Government, 1985 (Box 5)
  - National Housing Hall of Fame, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Mortgage Bankers, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Virginia Committee of Professional Development, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Single Family Bond Closing, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Rural Homesteading drawing, 1985 (Box 5)
  - Tri-State MBA Servicing Clinic, 1985 (Box 5)
  - HIE Workshops (Lynchburg, Danville, Bristol, Roanoke, Springfield), 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Internal Auditor, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - United Way, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - VHDA 5 Year Plan, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: U.S. Legislators, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: State Legislators, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Executive Division: Meetings and Speaking Engagements, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: Director, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: Complaints, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: Bond Call (1986), 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: Bonds - Veterans, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Finance Division: Moody's rating letters (1985 and previous), 1985 (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: Director, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: Moderate Rehabilitation, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing, 1985-1986 (Box 6)
  - Legal Division, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Multifamily Division: Director, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Multifamily Division: Greenfield Plantation, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Multifamily Division: Rural Homesteading, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rental Rehabilitation, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rural Homesteading, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Director, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Complaints, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Attorney General, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Dislocated Worker Program, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Wednesday Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Curry Roberts, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Governor, Office of the: Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Governor, Office of the: Policy memos, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Governor, Office of the: Governor's Sporting League, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Miscellaneous state agencies, 1985-1986 (Box 7)
  - Legislative - General Assembly, 1985 (Box 7)
- Correspondence, subject files, and board meeting records (Accession 44568), 1972-1988 (bulk 1985-1988)., Extent: 9 cu. ft. (9 boxes).
  Original arragement maintained.
  - Housing Study Commission, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Human Services, Secretary of: Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Human Services, Secretary of: Migrant Worker Tour, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Human Services, Secretary of: Shelter Tours, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Human Services, Secretary of: Virginia Interagency Migrant Worker Commission, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous state agencies, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Commission on Housing the Disabled, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Interagency Initiative Group on Housing for Persons with Disabilities, 1986 (Box 1)
  - DMHMR Research Project, 1985 (Box 1)
  - DMHMR Interagency Planning Council, 1985 (Box 1)
  - DMHMR Congregate Home Program, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - Transportation in the 21st Century, 1985-1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: HB 898, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: HB 1223, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: HB 1248, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: HB 1664, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Committees, Offices, etc., 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Legislative memos, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Legislative status memos, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Miscellaneous bills and resolutions, 1987 (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Legislative Services - General Laws Subcommittee Studying Housing in Urban AReas, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Planning and Research Division: MCC - Mobile homes, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Planning and Research Division: New Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rental Rehab, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Single Family Division: Director, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Single Family Division: Complaints, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Single Family Division: Single Family Funds, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Single Family Division: Mobilie Homes, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Commonwealth, Secretary of the, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Wednesday Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Economic Development, Secretary of: Retreat, 1987 (Box 2)
  - Govenor's Office: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 2)
  - Govenor's Office: Audited Financials, 1982-1984 (Box 2)
  - Govenor's Office: Executive Orders, 1976-1984 (Box 2)
  - Executive Division: Director, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Huff, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Budget, 1982-1984 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: U.S. Legislators, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: State Legislators, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Executive Division: Meetings and Speaking Engagements, 1986-1987 (Box 3)
  - Administration Division: Director, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Administration Division: Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Administration Division: New Building - Contracts and Reports, 1985-1987 (Box 4)
  - Administration Division: Computer Operations, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Administration Division: Public Relations - Annual Reports, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Administration Division: Public Relations - Newsletter, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
  - Executive Division: Special Projects, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: VHF, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: Director, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Finance Division: Interest Rate Projections, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Director, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Mod Rehab, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Housing Management Division: Rental Rehab, 1987 (Box 5)
  - Legal Division: Director, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Legal Division: Policy Statements, 1972-1978 (Box 5)
  - Legal Division: Barton, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Multifamily Division: Director, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Multifamily Division: Loan Program, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Multifamily Division: New Briarfield Apartments, 1986 (Box 5)
  - Multifamily Division: Tobacco Row Associates, 1986-1987 (Box 5)
  - Executive Division: Internal Auditor - PMM, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Strategic Planning, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Task Forces, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - General (Disabled, Elderly, Energy, MCC, Outreach, Political, Purchase/Rehab, Single Family), 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - United Way Campaign, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Alexandria Chamber of Commerce on Housing, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Bond Allocation, 1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Emergency Shelter Program, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Focus Group findings, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Housing Conditions, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Virginia Housing Initiatives, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Fairfax Proposal, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Housing Needs information, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Ivanhoe, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Low Income Housing Credit, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Northern Virginia Housing Coalition, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Oil Overcharge Funds, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Real Estate Advisory Board, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Revolving Loan Fund, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Revision of Multifamily Loan Program, 1986 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: St. Paul's College Single Parent Program, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Special Projects: Virginia Housing Coalition, 1986-1987 (Box 6)
  - Administrative Services Division: Director, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services Division: AIDS Program, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services Division: General Staff Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services Division: New Building Site - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services Division: New Building Site - Child Care Center Task Force, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services Division: New Building Site - Office Space Increase, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services Division: Computer Operations, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services Division: Public Information, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Administrative Services Division: Support Services, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Director, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Commissioners, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: U.S. Legislators, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: State Legislators, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Meetings and Speaking Engagements, 1987-1988 (Box 7)
  - Executive Division: Meetings and Speaking Engagements, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Executive Division: Miscellaneous, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Affordability, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Alexandria Chamber of Commerce, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Bond Allocation, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Emergency Shelter Program, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Home Builders Advisory Board, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Housing Initiatives, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Lee Gardens, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Southwest Virginia Office, 1987-1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Virginia Housing Coalition, 1988 (Box 8)
  - Special Projects: Virginia Housing Fund, 1987 (Box 9)
  - Finance Division: Director, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Finance Division: Bond Counsel and Underwriters Fees, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management Division: Director, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management Division: HUD Audit Report, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management Division: Loan Review Task Force, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management Division: Project Reserves, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management Division: Refinance Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management Division: Moderate Rehab, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management Division: New Construction, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Housing Management Division: Section 8 Existing, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Legal Division, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Multifamily Division: Director, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Multifamily Division: HUD Co-insurer, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Multifamily Division: Mortgage Loan Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Planning and Research Division: Director, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Planning and Research Division: Rental Rehabilitation, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Single Family Division: Director, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Single Family Division: Complaints, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
  - Single Family Division: Servicing, 1987-1988 (Box 9)
- Correspondence, subject files, and board meeting records (Accession 44640), 1977-1990 (bulk 1987-1990)., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  - Executive: Secretary of Administration, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development, 1988 Jan-June (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development, 1988 Jul-Dec (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development - Meeting with Deputy Secretary, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: State Fair, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Study Commission (E129), 1987 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Study Commission (E129) - Hearing, 1988 Aug (Box 1)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Study Commission (E129) - Organizational meeting, 1988 May (Box 1)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Study Commission (E129) - Meeting, 1988 Nov (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of Education, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of Human Resources, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of Human Resources - Migrant Worker Committee, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of Human Resources - Committee on Housing the Disabled, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of Transportation and Public Safety, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Attorney General, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Governor's Office, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Governor's Office - Executive Decision Documents, 1987 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Governor's Office - Innovative Programs, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: General Assembly, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: General Assembly - HB 997, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: General Assembly - Calendar, Committees, etc., 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: General Assembly - Governor's Budget Proposal for Housing, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: General Assembly - Status of Legislative Memos, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: HUD - Budget, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: HUD - Central, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: HUD - D.C. Area Office, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: HUD - Region III Philadelphia, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Executive: HUD - Richmond Area Office, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Administrative Services: Director, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Bew building site, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: New building site, 1989 Jan-June (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: New building site - Kjellstrom and Lee, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: New building opening, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: New building opening - Plaque, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Labor and Industry - Purchase/Lease, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Management information systems, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Personnel Dept., 1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Public relations, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Social Committee, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Support Services, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Training and development, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Annual Report, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Administrative Services: Balance Sheet/Newsletter, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Director, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Budget, 1988-1989 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Commissioners, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Legislators, U.S., 1989 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Legislators, State, 1989 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Governor's Housing Conference, 1988 Sept (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc., 1989 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Commissioner's Retreat, 1988 (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - National Housing and Rehabilitation Association, 1988 Aug (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Low Income Tax Credit Seminar, 1989 Mar (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Virginia Tech lecture class, 1989 Mar (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Homebuilders Association of Virginia, 1989 Apr (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Arlington Housing Corp., 1989 Mar (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Fairfax/Falls Church CSB dinner, 1989 Mar (Box 2)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Virginia Center for Housing conference, 1989 May-June (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Arlington Housing Corp., 1989 June (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Testimony before General Assembly, 1989 Aug (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Trends in Housing Round Table, 1989 Aug (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Federal Home Loan Bank of Atlanta seminar, 1989 Sept (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Virginia Executive Institute, 1989 Oct (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Meeting with Page Bond re: Time management system, 1989 Oct (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Downtown Roanoke Task Force, 1989 Nov (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Nelson County / Virginia Water Project / Monticello Area Community Action Agency meeting, 1989 Nov (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Glade Hill, 1989 Dec (Box 3)
  - Executive: Meetings, Speaking engagements, etc. - Lynchburg Group Home opening and ceremony, 1989 Dec (Box 3)
  - Executive: RFP - Audit, 1988-1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Financial statement, 1977-1986 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Management letter (FY 1980), 1980 (Box 3)
  - Executive: United Way, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Alexandria Chamber, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Emergency Shelter Program, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Homeless, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Migrant Housing, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Non-Profit Housing Groups, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Northern Virginia Building Industry Association, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Real Estate Advisory Board, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Single Room Occupancy, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Coalition, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund, 1988 July-Dec (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund, 1989 Jan-Apr (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund, 1989 May-Aug (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund - Fund Committee, 1989 Apr (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund - Recyling, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund - Round Two Single Family Affordable Housing Program, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund -, 1987-1988 (Box 3)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund - Interest rates, 1988 (Box 3)
  - Finance: Director, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Finance: Moody's Rating Letters, 1987 (Box 3)
  - Finance: Moody's Rating Letters, 1986 (Box 3)
  - Housing Management: Director, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management: Moderate rehabilitation, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management: Hubert Young, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management: New construction, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management: Section 8 existing, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Housing Management: Vouchers, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Legal: General Counsel, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Legal: Christian Barton, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Multi-Family: Director, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Multi-Family: Benton Mortgage Company proposal, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Multi-Family: Low Income Housing Tax Credits, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
  - Multi-Family: Mortgage Loan Committee, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Multi-Family: 80/20 Program - Discussions with Commissioner Cooper, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research: Director, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research: Rental rehabilitation, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research: Senior home equity, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Planning and Research: Senior home equity account, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Single Family: Director, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Single Family: Complaints, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Single Family: Murphy Group, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Single Family: New program ideas, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Single Family: Servicing, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Administration, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development, 1989 Jan-Mar (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development, 1989 Apr-June (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development, 1989 July-Sept (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development - Monthly meetings, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development - Achievements, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development - Annual Retreat, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development - Semi-monthly reports, 1989 (Box 4)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Fund, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Partnership Fund, 1988 (Box 4)
  - Executive: Secretary of Administration, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Economic Development, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Partnership Fund, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Dept. of Housing and Community Development - Virginia Housing Partnership Fund, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Economic Development and Natural Resources Subcommittee, 1988 Feb (Box 5)
  - Executive: Memos, 1988 Feb (Box 5)
  - Executive: House Appropriations, 1988 Jan (Box 5)
  - Executive: Virginia Housing Study Commission (E-139), 1988 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Health and Human Resources - Migrant Worker Committee, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Health and Human Resources - SAVE Task Force, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Health and Human Resources - Mental Health / VHDA Congregate Home Program, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Health and Human Resources - Mental Health Planning Council, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Health and Human Resources - Committee on Housing the Disabled, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Health and Human Resources - Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Secretary of Transportation, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Governor's Office, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Miscellaneous state agencies, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Dept. of Legislative Services, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: HUD - Central, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: HUD - DC Area Office, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: HUD - Region III Philadelphia, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: HUD - Richmond Area Office, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: National Housing and Rehabilitation Association, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Low Income Housing Information Service Roundup, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Virginia Association of Housing and Community Development Officials, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Virginia Association of Housing and Community Development Officials - Annual meeting, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Executive: Virginia Association of Housing and Community Development Officials - Workshop, 1989 Jan (Box 5)
  - Administrative Services: Director, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Administrative Services: Dependent Care Committee, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Administrative Services: New Building - General correspondence, 1990 (Box 5)